capetownetc.com 2017-02-13

# Privacy Policy | CapeTown ETC

PRIVACY POLICY

THIS PRIVACY POLICY (“POLICY”) GOVERNS THE COLLECTION,

MANAGEMENT AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT

HIGHBURY MEDIA (PTY) LTD (“HM,” “we” OR “us”) COLLECTS THROUGH

THE FOLLOWING WEBSITES:

http://www.dash4cash.com

http://www.sarugbymagazine.com

http://www.capetownetc.com

http://www.weddingalbum.co.za

http://www.sacricketmag.com

http://www.sasoccermag.co.za

http://www.sportsclub.co.za

http://aa.co.za

http://www.compleatgolfer.co.za

http://www.mykitchen.co.za

(“THE WEBSITES”).

WE RESPECT YOUR RIGHTS TO RESPONSIBLE MANAGEMENT OF

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION UNDER THE PROTECTION OF

PERSONAL INFORMATION ACT 4 OF 2013. YOUR USE OF THE

WEBSITES AND HM’S PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IS SUBJECT TO THIS

POLICY. BY USING THE WEBSITES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO

PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE

WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY TERM

IN THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITES OR SUBMIT

ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THROUGH THE

WEBSITES.

1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

1.1 HM and/or its authorised technology agents may collect and store

certain Personal Information from You in connection with Your use of

THE WEBSITES and/or the products and/services provided to You by

HM.

1.2 For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information is defined

in accordance with the definition in the Act. Generally, such

information is information that can be used to personally identify you. In

particular, however, HM may collect information such as:

1.2.1 first name and surname,

1.2.2 email address,

1.2.3 cell phone number,

1.2.4 profession or occupation,

from the following persons: any individual who chooses to register on

THE WEBSITES.

1.3 HM may also automatically collect and store non-personally identifiable

information related to your use of the THE WEBSITES. Non-personally

identifiable information may include personal information that has been

aggregated.

1.4 We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties

for certain reasons, including advertising, marketing and/or other

purposes.

1.5 Your Personal Information is used to provide You with the requested

products and/or services; enable ease of use of THE WEBSITES;

process transactions concluded by You; engage in electronic

communications and transactions with You; administer promotions or

survey or similar interactive activity; or to provide You with newsletters

or other periodic communications and/or marketing materials.

1.6 Personal Information is automatically collected in relation to Your visit

to THE WEBSITES, such information includes but is not limited to:

Your browser type and version, as well as Your operating system.

1.7 Cookies are small files send from THE WEBSITES to a Your computer

drive that can be used to track when You visit and re-visit a website

and how you behave on websites. HM may use cookies to identify the

device with which You access THE WEBSITES and may use

anonymous cookies to determine website usage analytics and statistics

in order to optimise THE WEBSITES and Your experience. You are

able to manually delete cookies from Your browser or set Your browser

to reject cookies. PLEASE NOTE that certain pages or features may

not be available or work correctly if You have set Your browser to reject

cookies.

1.8 HM uses Google Analytics and Effective Measures, which supports

data collection without browser cookies. It helps HM to understand user

interaction with THE WEBSITES and implement changes that evolve

THE WEBSITES to suit Your needs.

1.9 The WEBSITES hosting agents and/or service providers may

automatically log Your “IP address” which is a unique identifier for Your

computer and/or other access device. Such information collected is for

aggregate purposes only and cannot be used to identify You

personally.

1.10 In the event that You subscribe to newsletters and/or to receive further

information through other periodic communications, from HM, Your

Personal Information will be processed by HM to provide You with such

information and associated processes. All HM communications shall

contain an unsubscribe link and by following the unsubscribe process

You shall be removed from the relevant distribution list and HM shall no

longer send You the subscription information. Should you experience

any issues with this process please contact our legal advisor, Tracey

Stewart at tracey@hsm.co.za directly.

2\. CONSENT TO PROCESS PERSONAL INFORMATION

2.1 You understand that Your consent to the processing of your personal

information by HM pertains to the provision of the products and

services made available on THE WEBSITES; as well as associated

purposes. Processing shall include the collection, receipt, recording,

organisation, collation, storage, updating or modification, retrieval,

alteration, consultation, use; dissemination by means of transmission,

distribution or making available in any other form; or merging, linking,

as well as blocking, degradation, erasure or destruction of information.

2.2 This consent is effective from the moment you access THE WEBSITES

and will endure until Your access and/or relationship with HM has been

terminated.

2.3 You expressly consent to HM retaining Your Personal Information once

your relationship with HM has been terminated for: aggregate,

statistical and reporting purposes.

2.4 In the event that You wish to revoke all consent pertaining to Your

Personal Information and You would like HM to remove and/or delete

Your Personal Information entirely, You must notify HM via email to

HM’s legal advisor, Tracey Stewart email address: tracey@hsm.co.za.

2.5 By Using THE WEBSITES, You represent that You are of the age of 18

or that a Competent Person has given consent to allow Your minor

child to utilise THE WEBSITES. You, or a ‘Competent Person’ in the

case of a minor, consent/s to the processing of personal information

that belongs to You or, in the case of a minor, to the minor for whom

You are responsible, in the manner described in this Policy. You agree

that giving such consent means that You have given HM permission to

collect and process the child’s personal information in the ways

described in this Policy.

3\. HANDLING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

3.1 HM endeavors to comply with all laws and regulations pertaining to

information and communications privacy including, but not limited to,

the 1996 South African Constitution and the Protection of Personal

Information Act 4 of 2013 (“the Act”). HM applies the principles of

protection of personal information under such Act in further legislation

referred to in the Act.

3.2 You have the right to correct Your Personal Information as well as to

revoke Your consent to the processing of Your Personal Information by

HM. You do, however, understand that HM requires Your Personal

Information to render the HM products and/or services and should You

decide to revoke Your consent HM may not be able to provide You with

such products and/or services.

3.3 HM will take all reasonable measures in order to ensure Your Personal

Information is appropriately safeguarded, these precautions include,

but are not limited to: the use of a sufficiently secure server and

providing suitably secure payment mechanisms.

3.4 Should any unauthorised person/s gain access to Your personal

information HM will contact You within a reasonable time to inform You

of the security breach.

3.5 HM seeks to ensure the quality, accuracy and confidentiality of

Personal Information in its possession.

3.6 HM may share Your personal information with authorised third parties

these include persons such as employees and service providers to HM.

HM does not permit these parties to use such information for any other

purpose than to perform the services that HM has instructed them to

provide and in accordance with this Policy.

3.7 From time to time, HM may appoint certain agents, third parties and/or

service providers which operate outside the borders of the Republic of

South Africa. In these circumstances HM will be required to transmit

Your Personal Information outside South Africa. The purpose of the

trans-border flow of Your Personal Information may include, but is not

limited to: data hosting and storage. You expressly consent to the

trans-border flow of Your Personal Information. Furthermore, You

warrant in this regard that You have obtained the necessary consents

required in terms of the Act, in order to enable the trans-border flow of

any personal information submitted by You. HM warrants in this regard

that it shall only engage the services of third parties (in relation to the

aforesaid trans-border flow of information) which subscribe acceptable

safeguards in accordance with HM’s legal obligations.

3.8 HM will not sell, exchange or transfer Your Personal Information to any

third party except as required in the provision of the HM products

and/or services and in accordance with the consents provided by You.

3.9 HM will make amendments and/or updates to this Privacy Policy on

occasion. Amendments made to this Policy shall become immediately

effective. We encourage You to periodically review this Policy to keep

informed about how HM is protecting Your Personal Information. You

can find the last date of change made to the Policy above for Your

reference. Your continued Use of THE WEBSITES evidences Your

acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any updates made to it.

3.10 THE WEBSITES may contain links to other WEBSITES. HM is not

responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.

4\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

4.1 Records relating to the provision of the HM products and/or services by

HM to You and the Personal Information submitted by You may be

required to be retained in terms of legislated records retention

requirements, HM’s operational purposes and/or for production as

evidence by HM in legal proceedings.

4.2 HM may disclose Your Personal Information under the following

circumstances:

4.2.1 To comply with the law or with legal process;

4.2.2 To protect and defend HM’s rights, equipment, facilities and other

property;

4.2.3 To protect HM against misuse or unauthorised use of THE WEBSITES

and/or products and/or services; and/or

4.2.4 To protect other WEBSITES their Users or third parties affected

negatively by Your actions in use of the products/services and/or THE

WEBSITES

5\. OBJECTIONS, COMPLAINTS AND QUERIES

5.1 Should You require a correction to be made to Your Personal

Information that HM keeps on record, or a copy of the record itself, or

should You feel that You would like to object to the collection, Use or

processing of Your Personal Information by HM, or that you would like

us to delete your personally identifiable information, then kindly send

an e-mail to our Information Officer, whose name and details are set

out below. We will endeavour to make the correction, provide You with

the record (We reserve our right to charge a small fee in this case),

cease processing of Your Personal Information and/or delete it, in

accordance with Your request.

INFORMATION OFFICER: HM LEGAL ADVISOR – TRACEY STEWART

EMAIL ADDRESS: tracey@hsm.co.za

TEL: 021 416 0141
